ingimage.com 2019-01-16

# Privacy Policy

### Ingram Image

13 Monmouth Street, London WC2H 9DA (registered co 02949455) Tel 020 632 0220

1\. This policy sets out how we handle your personal information if you’re an Ingram Image user or visitor to our Sites. It applies across all Ingram Image sites and affiliated sites including, inter alia, ingimage.com, signelements.com, vectorstate.com (the “Sites”).  
When we say ‘we’, ‘us’ or ‘Ingram Image’ it’s because that’s who we are and we own and/or run the Sites. For the purposes of applicable EU data protection law (including the General Data Protection Regulation 2016/679 (the “GDPR”), we are a ‘data controller’ of your personal information.

**The type of personal information we collect**

2\. We collect certain personal information about visitors and users of our Sites.  
3\. The most common types of information we collect include things like: user-names, member names, email addresses, IP addresses, other contact details, survey responses, blogs, photos, payment information such as payment agent details, transactional details, tax information, support queries, forum comments, content you direct us to make available on our Sites (such as item descriptions and meta data). We will also collect personal information from job applications (such as, your CV, the application form itself, cover letter and interview notes).

**How we collect personal information**

4\. We collect personal information directly when you provide it to us, automatically as you navigate through the Sites, or through other people when you use services associated with the Sites.  
5\. We collect your personal information when you provide it to us when you complete membership registration and buy or provide items or services on our Sites, subscribe to a newsletter, email list, submit feedback, enter a contest, fill out a survey, or send us a communication.

**Personal information we collect about you from others**

6\. Although we generally collect personal information directly from you, on occasion, we also collect certain categories of personal information about you from other sources. In particular:  
1\. financial and/or transaction details from payment providers located in the UK, US, and elsewhere in order to process a transaction;  
2\. other third party sources/ and or partners, whereby we receive additional information about you (to the extent permitted by applicable law), such as demographic data or fraud detection information, and combine it with information we have about you. We also receive information about you as a rights holder from our third party contributors. For example, information in the form of a model release when your image is used in an item made available on our Sites.

**How we use personal information**

7\. We will use your personal information:  
1\. To fulfil a contract, or take steps linked to a contract: in particular, in facilitating and processing transactions that take place on the Sites, such as when you purchase a subscription from one of our sites.  
2\. Where this is necessary for purposes which are in our, or third parties, legitimate interests. These interests include:  
1\. operating the Sites;  
2\. providing you with services described on the Sites;  
3\. verifying your identity when you sign in to any of our Sites;  
4\. responding to support issues, and helping facilitate the resolution of any disputes;  
5\. updating you with operational news and information about our Sites and services e.g. to notify you about changes to our Sites, website disruptions or security updates;  
6\. carrying out technical analysis to determine how to improve the Sites and services we provide;  
7\. monitoring activity on the Sites, e.g. to identify potential fraudulent activity and to ensure compliance with the user terms that apply to the Sites;  
8\. managing our relationship with you, e.g. by responding to your comments or queries submitted to us on the Sites or asking for your feedback or whether you want to participate in a survey;  
9\. managing our legal and operational affairs (including, managing risks relating to content and fraud matters);  
10\. training Ingram Image staff about how to best serve our clients;  
11\. improving our products and services.  
12\. providing general administrative and performance functions and activities; and  
13\. processing your job application to Ingram Image.  
14\. providing you with marketing information about products and services which we feel may interest you; and

**When we disclose your personal information**

8\. We will disclose personal information to the following recipients:  
1\. companies that are in the Ingram Image group;  
2\. subcontractors and service providers who assist us in connection with the ways we use personal information (as set out above), in particular: website hosting provider Impactinit which are located in Holland and Spain; technical and customer support services, including but not limited to Intercom.com LLC and Mailchimp, which are located in UK, Holland, France, Spain and the US; recruitment agencies which are located in the UK, US and Holland; marketing and analytics services which are located in the UK and US; our professional advisers (lawyers, accountants, financial advisers etc.) which are located in the UK;  
3\. regulators and government authorities in connection with our compliance procedures and obligations;  
4\. a purchaser or prospective purchaser of all or part of our assets or our business, and their professional advisers, in connection with the purchase;  
5\. a third party to respond to requests relating to a criminal investigation or alleged or suspected illegal activity;  
6\. a third party, in order to enforce or defend our rights, or to address financial or reputational risks;  
7\. a rights holder in relation to an allegation of intellectual property infringement or any other infringement; and  
8\. other recipients where we are authorised or required by law to do so.

**Where we transfer and/or store your personal information**

9\. We are based in the UK so your data will be processed in the UK. Some of the recipients we have described in section 8 above, and to whom we disclose your personal information, are based outside the UK. We do this on the basis of your consent to this policy. In order to protect your information, we take care where possible to work with subcontractors and service providers who we believe maintain an acceptable standard of data security compliance.

**How we keep your personal information secure**

10\. We store personal information on secure servers that are managed by us and our service providers, and occasionally hard copy files that are kept in a secure location in the UK. Personal information that we store or transmit is protected by security and access controls. How you can access your personal information  
11\. You can access some of the personal information that we collect about you by logging in to your account. You also have the right to make a request to access other personal information we hold about you and to request corrections of any errors in that data. You can also close the account you have with us for any of our Sites at any time. To make an access or correction request, contact our Data Protection Officer using the contact details at the end of this policy.

 **Marketing Choices regarding your personal information**

12\. From time to time, we send you marketing communications by email about products and services that we feel may be of interest to you. You can ‘opt-out’ of such communications if you would prefer not to receive them in the future by using the “unsubscribe” facility provided in the communication itself.  
13\. You also have choices about cookies, as described below. By modifying your browser preferences, you have the choice to accept all cookies, to be notified when a cookie is set, or to reject all cookies. If you choose to reject cookies some parts of our Sites may not work properly in your case.

**Cookies and web analytics**

14\. When you visit our Sites, there’s certain information that’s recorded which is generally anonymous information and does not reveal your identity. If you’re logged into your account some of this information could be associated with your account. We’re talking about the following kinds of details:  
1\. your IP address or proxy server IP address’;  
2\. the domain name you requested;  
3\. the name of your internet service provider is sometimes captured depending on the configuration of your ISP connection;  
4\. the date and time of your visit to the website;  
5\. the length of your session;  
6\. the pages which you have accessed;  
7\. the number of times you access our site within any month;  
8\. the file URL you look at and information relating to it;  
9\. the website which referred you to our Sites; and  
10\. the operating system which your computer uses.  
15\. Occasionally, we will use third party advertising companies to serve ads based on prior visits to our Sites. For example, if you visit our Sites, you may later see an advert for our products and services when you visit a different Site.

**Information about children**

16\. Our Sites are not suitable for children under the age of 16 years, so if you are under 16 we ask that you do not use our Sites or give us your personal information. If you are from 16 to 18 years, you can browse the Sites but you’ll need the supervision of a parent or guardian to become a registered user. It’s the responsibility of parents or guardians to monitor their children’s use of our Sites.

**How long we keep your personal information**

17\. We retain your personal information for as long as is necessary to provide the services to you and others, and to comply with our legal obligations. If you no longer want us to use your personal information or to provide you with our services, you can request that we erase your personal information and close your Ingram account. Please note that if you request the erasure of your personal information we will retain information from deleted accounts as necessary for our legitimate business interests, to comply with the law, prevent fraud, collect fees, resolve disputes, troubleshoot problems, assist with investigations, enforce the terms of service and take other actions permitted by law. The information we retain will be handled in accordance with this Privacy Policy.

**When we need to update this policy**

18\. We will need to change this policy from time to time in order to make sure it stays up to date with the latest legal requirements and any changes to our privacy management practices.  
19\. When we do change the policy, we’ll make sure to notify you about such changes, where required. A copy of the latest version of this policy will always be available on this page.

**How you can contact us**

20\. If you have any questions about our privacy practices or the way in which we have been managing your personal information, please contact our Data Protection Officer in writing to Data Protection Officer, Ingram Image, 13 Monmouth Street, London WC2H 9DA or email info@ingrampublishing.com SUBJECT – Data Protection.  
How you can complain if you are not satisfied with our effort to resolve any privacy issues which might occur:  
If you have unresolved concerns you also have the right to complain to data protection authorities. The relevant data protection authority will be the data protection authority of the country: (i) of your habitual residence; (ii) of your place of work; or (iii) in which you consider the alleged infringement has occurred. Both personal information and personal data have the same meaning in the context of this Privacy Policy. Ingram Image Privacy Policy, effective date 25 May 2018
